oneall.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy | www.oneall.com

Last Modified: February 15, 2012

#### **We value your privacy**

We take your privacy very seriously and we will not share any information you give us with anyone else unless required by law. We will never sell, rent or otherwise distribute the information that you or your users share with us. We value your privacy and we want you to feel comfortable using our services. 

## About us

OneAll Sàrl (“OneAll”, ”we”, ”us”) is a registered technology company offering a set of web-delivered tools and services for establishing and optimizing a site’s connection with many social networks and providers such as Facebook, Twitter, Yahoo! and LinkedIn amongst others. 

The OneAll social optimization platform enables online businesses (“Developers”) to (a) easily connect their sites to all the major social platforms and integrate with Open ID and other external authentication providers; (b) offer their site visitors (“End Users”) on-site authentication, sharing and social features to enhance their connected experience; and (c) analyze a site’s social activity with helpful use data and metrics. 

OneAll’s technology also enables Developers and their End Users to easily distribute web content applications such as photos, videos and other widgets (“Web Applications”) to social networks and a wide variety of other web destinations, and directly to mobile devices. 

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our privacy practices as they pertain to our website, oneall.com (the “Site”) and subdomains of this domain. We also intend for this policy to inform you about our privacy practices as they pertain to your use of our Web Applications and services (collectively, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy applies to all aspects of the Service, whether made available or accessed via our Site, via the websites of our partners, via other third parties, or on mobile devices. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

## 1\. Personally Identifiable Information

We collect personally identifiable information (“PII”) via the Site and the Service. PII is any information that may be used to contact, identify or locate an individual, and includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, email address and postal addresses. OneAll generally collects PII under the following scenarios: 

  1. When you choose to provide us with your PII via the Site; including, when you send us an email asking a question, we use that information to answer your question and will store it for a reasonable time. 
  2. We may periodically publish an email newsletter. If you provide us with your email address for the purposes of receiving OneAll’s email newsletter, we may also email you with further information and offers from OneAll and/or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided within the email. 
  3. The Service may enable you to send emails to your friends. If you provide your email address or your friends’ email addresses for these purposes, OneAll will store those email addresses, but will not use them to send promotional emails to you or your friends (unless you or your friends independently sign up to receive promotional emails from OneAll.) 
  4. When Developers and OneAll Clients register to use the Service via the Site, OneAll collects their name, company, email address, website URL and telephone number. OneAll also asks them to select a password for their account. OneAll uses this information to help maintain their account. 
  5. If you choose to use the Service via one of the many open standards for user authentication and access control (e.g., OpenID, OAuth, etc.) that enable you to link the Service with accounts you have already established with social networking platforms (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, etc.) and/or email platforms (e.g., Yahoo! Mail), OneAll will collect the PII as well as other information that you have already provided to the social networking or email platform. This PII may include your name, email address, postal address, and demographic information such as age, gender and income. Although OneAll won’t use your PII in this manner without your affirmative (“Opt-in”) consent, OneAll may use the information collected this way to analyze the usage of the Service and/or to compile anonymous statistics. In all instances, OneAll obtains and uses this information in accordance with the policies of the social networking or email platform. 
  6. When Developers or Clients use the Service and collect PII, OneAll will immediately transfer the PII back to the Developer or Client and cache such PII for a reasonable time, in order to improve the performance of the service. Please note that information collected by such Web Applications is subject to that particular Developer or Client’s privacy policy, and that OneAll is merely facilitating the collection and transfer of the PII in accordance with that privacy policy. OneAll takes reasonable steps to ensure that our Developers and Clients update their privacy policies accordingly. 
  7. End Users may be afforded the opportunity to deploy emails via the Service. Where End Users have selected the option of adding one or more email addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent to those email addresses on their behalf. These email addresses will be stored in the address book the OneAll End User creates and will be used only for the purpose of sending the email communication to the addressee. OneAll cautions all End Users to utilize this email functionality in a responsible manner. 

## 2\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

OneAll also collects non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) via the Site and Service. Non-PII is information that may not, on its own, be used to identify or locate a personal or entity, and includes your IP address, browser type, and your computer’s operating system. OneAll collects Non-PII under the following scenarios: 

  1. When you visit the Site, our servers automatically collect Non-PII, including but not limited to your IP address, the number, frequency and duration of your visit to the Site and specific pages viewed, your browser type, your Internet Service Provider, your computer's operating system, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site, and information you search for on the Site. This information is used for Site maintenance, to improve the relevance of the content that you see, and for reporting purposes. 
  2. When you register on the Site, the OneAll servers automatically collect the Non-PII items described above as well as your interactions with OneAll’s staff and other registered Site users. We retain this Non-PII in our internal system as part of your registered account. We use this information internally to analyze the aggregate activities and preferences of our registered Site users, and to track and assess your interest in becoming a paid subscriber to the Service 
  3. When you use the Service, the OneAll servers automatically collect Non-PII including but not limited to your IP address, web pages viewed (including but not limited to web pages where Web Applications(s) are located, your browser type, your Internet Service Provider, your interactions with OneAll’s Web Applications (e.g., the amount of time you spent viewing a video embedded within a Web Application), the web page you were visiting before you came to the Service, and information you search for via the Service. This information is used for Site maintenance, to improve the relevance of the content that you see, and for reporting purposes. Please note that Web Developers and Clients may also collect Non-PII as it pertains to their Web Applications, and that the information collected by the Service and transferred to Clients and Developers is subject to that particular Developer or Client’s privacy policy. OneAll takes reasonable steps to ensure that our Developers and Clients update their privacy policies accordingly. 
  4. When you create a Web Application which is using the Service, OneAll may record data related to that activity, including but not limited to the URL of the web page(s) where the Web Application is deployed. We use that information to help maintain and track the effectiveness of the Service. 

## 3\. Cookies and Tracking Pixels

OneAll uses “cookies” in connection with the Site and the Service. A cookie is a small data file that the OneAll servers transfer to your computer for record-keeping purposes. OneAll uses “persistent cookies” to save your username and login password for future logins to the Site and the Service. OneAll uses “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Service. OneAll also uses “flash cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, and to help store the non-PII we use to deliver more relevant content to you via the Site, the Service, and on other websites you may visit. OneAll also use web beacons in connection with the Site and Service. Tracking pixels (also known as “1x1 pixels” or “clear GIFs”) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. 

## 4\. Third Party Data Collection

OneAll may use third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect Non-PII (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter, and certain demographic information such as age and gender) when you visit the OneAll Site and/or use the Service(s). Please note that some Non-PII (which does not include demographic information) is also collected from End Users who simply visit the Site and/or visit a web page where the Service is enabled. Please note that the OneAll Service facilitates the sharing of Web Applications across many different websites, and that it may not be obvious that a Web Application is present on any particular website that you are visiting. 

## 5\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

In addition to the data collection and use practices outlined above, we may share or otherwise disclose information to third parties under the following circumstances. 

### 5.1. Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

OneAll may share aggregated information with Clients, Developers, prospective Clients and prospective Developers as well as the press in order to demonstrate usage of the Service, spot industry trends, and to generate publicity for the Service. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain PII. 

### 5.2. Service Providers

OneAll may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Service and/or to provide services on it`s behalf, (including, without limitation, bill and credit card payment processing, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics and administration). These third parties have access to PII only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated by contract not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

### 5.3 Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

OneAll cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. OneAll will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as OneAll, in it`s sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of OneAll or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity OneAll may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. 

### 5.4 Business Transfers

OneAll may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including PII and any other information it has, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. 

## 6\. Changing or Deleting Your Information

Anyone with a registered OneAll account may review, update, correct or delete the PII in their registration profile by logging into their account and changing the “End User preferences” associated with their account. OneAll may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. If you’d like OneAll to delete any PII that it has on you, please send an email to privacy@oneall.com. 

## 7\. Information Security

The security of your information is important to us, including but not limited to the PII collected via the Site and Service. We have implemented reasonable security measures to protect the information in our care, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to the use of firewalls and encryption. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## 8\. Storage in the European Union

Information collected on this Site or via the Service may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the European Union and choose to provide information to OneAll, please be advised that we transfer PII to the European Union and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your consent to that transfer. 

## 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we make any substantive changes in the way that we use the information collected through the Site or the Service, we will post a clear and conspicuous notice of those changes on the Site and in this privacy policy.
